techemergence.com 2019-11-30

# Privacy Policy | Emerj

#### **What Data We Collect, and How Data is Collected**

Our surveys and web forms ask visitors their name, name address, company, and the AI-related industries and business functions that they are interested in. This information is only collected when users choose to fill out surveys.

We use Google Analytics for on-site metrics, such as location, time-on-site, bounce rates, etc

####  **How We Use and Store Data**

Emerj uses survey and web-form data to tailor email messages (content, reports, services) to the users who have expressed specific interest. This data is stored within our CRM and email marketing software.

Emerj uses Google Analytics data to improve website content, determine new content topics, and aide with new features or redesigns.

####  **Cookies**

Cookies are text files placed on your computer to collect standard Internet log information and visitor behavior information. When you visit our websites, we may collect information from you automatically through cookies or similar technology (allaboutcookies.org).  

Our Company uses these cookies so that we recognize you on our website and remember your previously selected preferences, or to avoid re-loading content you’ve already seen.

You can set your browser not to accept cookies, and the above website tells you how to remove cookies from your browser. However, in a few cases, some of our website features may not function as a result.   

#### **Changes to our Privacy Policy**

Our Company keeps its privacy policy under regular review and places any updates on this web page. This privacy policy was last updated on July 14, 2019.   

#### **Contact Us**

How to contact us If you have any questions about Our Company’s privacy policy, the data we hold on you, or you would like to exercise one of your data protection rights, please do not hesitate to contact us. 

Email us at: info@emerj.com  
Call us: 1-617-945-8567
